你们准备点菜了吗
Hey. So you guys ready to order?
既然我们每个周二晚上6点都来
Since we come in every Tuesday night at 6:00
点完全一样的菜  现在是6:08分了
and order the same exact thing, and it's now 6:08
我想  不言而喻的不仅是这个问题
I believe your question not only answers itself
还有其他一些愚蠢的问题
but also stands alongside such other nonsensical queries
比如  "谁把狗放出来了"
as "Who let the dogs out?"
还有"他们过得如何"
And, uh, "How are they hanging""
好吧
Okay.
惯例  谢尔顿的汉堡上加一口唾沫
So, the usual, with extra spit on Sheldon's hamburger.
佩妮  等等
Penny, a moment?
这周末你有安排吗
Do you have plans this weekend?
天啊  艾米  很抱歉
Oh, gee, Amy, I'm sorry
我这周末真的很忙
I'm actually pretty busy this weekend.
可能要上今天点的菜
Probably serving food that was ordered today.
真不幸  我还想让你当我的伴儿
That's too bad. I was hoping you could be my plus-one
一起去多学科研究院
at the Institute of Interdisciplinary Studies'
参加现行科学研究
symposium on the impact of current scientific research
对社会交互的影响研讨会
on societal interactions.
什么
The what?
是一个年度科学会议
It's an annual science conference.
我们都被邀请发言
We've all been invited to speak.
哦  好吧  正如我说的  我有安排了
Oh! Oh, okay, well, you know, like I said, I have plans, so...
真可惜  因为你是我最好的朋友
Shame. Since you're my best friend
我还以为这是个增加交流的机会呢
I thought it would be a good bonding opportunity.
我是你最好的朋友吗
I'm your best friend?
你不看我的博客吗
Don't you read my blog?
别难过
Oh, don't feel bad.
我从来不看莱纳德的  我以前还跟他睡过
I never read Leonard's, and I used to sleep with him.
你认识其他会想去
Do you know anybody else who would appreciate
费用全包的大苏四星酒店
an all-expense-paid spa weekend
spa周末游的人吗
at a four-star resort in Big Sur?
不  我真的  对不起  免费什么  对不起  什么  什么
No, I really-- I'm sorry, free what? Sorry, what, what?
我想她周末突然没事了
I think her weekend just opened up.
等等  等等  我确认一下  你们说的spa
Wait, wait, just to be clear, when you guys say "Spa  "
跟普通人说的spa是一样的吗
does that mean the same thing as when regular people say it?
差不多
Pretty much.
除了我们穿着衣服蒸桑拿
Except we keep our shirts on in the sauna.
你知道吗  尽管会很难
You know, it is going to be difficult
但是我要取消我的安排  为了我的好朋友
but I'm going to cancel my plans so I can do this for my bestie.
请不要碰我的胸
Please don't touch my breasts.
我  我没想
I... I wasn't going to.
好吧  我只是要确定一下界限
All right. I just want to establish boundaries.
伙计们  这太棒了  我好久没度假了
Boy, this is great. I haven't had a vacation in ages.
想度假  先工作
In order to take a vacation, one first has to work.
知道吗  作为一个聪明人
You know, for a smart guy
你竟然不明白一个原则
you really seem to have a hard time grasping the concept
"不要惹给你准备饭的人"
"Don't piss off the people who handle the things you eat."
这原则确实很对
That does seem to be a valid principle.
我相信佩妮会遵守
I trust Penny will adhere to
"加州酒店员工
the "Official California Restaurant Workers'
道德和清洁庄严誓约"
Solemn Oath of Ethics and Cleanliness."
我认为没有这种东西
I don't believe there's any such thing.
你骗我
You lied to me?
生活大爆炸
第四季第十三集
早上好
Good morning.
大家请注意
If I could have everyone's attention, please?
我知道我们都想尽快开往大苏
I know we're all eager to get on the road to Big Sur
所以如果我们集中精神  我相信我们能
so if we focus, I'm sure we can get through this orientation
在半小时之内完成介绍
in under a half an hour.
就是些问答  测试  安全演习
Then it's just Q&A, quiz, safety drills
拍张团体纪念照  就能出发了
pose for commemorative group photo and we're off.
别担心  测试时坐我旁边
Don't worry. Just sit next to me during the quiz
你可以抄我的
and you can copy my answers.
拉杰
Raj?
你在干吗
What are you doing?
那可不行
I don't think so.
你的6盎司定额已经喝完了
You've had your allotted six ounces.
第一个上厕所时间是在贝克斯菲尔德的
The first bathroom break isn't until the Denny's
丹尼餐厅
located near Bakersfield
距此大约2个半小时
which is approximately two and half hours away.
记住  同志们
Remember, people
我们的强硬受制于最弱的膀胱
we're only as strong as our weakest bladder.
没人关心你的凯格尔练习
Nobody cares about your Kegel exercises.
好的  我们有7个人  2辆车
All right. We have seven people, and two cars.
领航车  由莱纳德驾驶
In the lead car, driven by Leonard
乘客是  我
will be... myself
艾米·费拉·福勒
Amy Farrah Fowler
和佩妮
and Penny.
耶
Yes!
他把你安排在另一个车上  我帮你升级了
He had you in the other car, but I got you upgraded.
耶
Yay!
她提出  如果我们在前不着村后不着店的地方
She made the case that if we break down
出故障  你在内布拉斯加边远地区的
in the middle of nowhere, your Nebraska backwoods skills
生存技能和健壮的大手能增加我们
and brawny hands will give us the best chance
在野外生存的机会
to survive in the wild.
健壮
Brawny?
比我的还大
They're bigger than mine.
红1号呼叫红5号  请回答
Red Leader to Red Five, come in.
霍华德  你保证过的
Howard, you promised.
好吧  红5号呼叫红1号
Fine. Red Five to Red Leader.
你要干吗
What do you want now?
现在是11:15
It's 11:15.
我要你每刻钟的位置报告
I'm requesting your quarter-hourly location update.
紧跟在你们后面呢
Still right behind you.
收到  红5号
Copy that, Red Five.
无线电联络就足够了
Radio contact is sufficient.
不需要伸你的中指
No need to extend your middle finger.
艾米  我在想
So, Amy, I've been wondering
你和谢尔顿要共住一间房吗
are you and Sheldon going to be sharing a room?
不  我们讨论过了
No, we discussed it.
一致认为  我们不想因为太了解对方
We decided we didn't want to jeopardize our relationship
而损害了我们的关系
by getting to know each other too well.
确实  没有比熟知对方的如厕规律
Indeed. Nothing sours a friendship more
更破坏友情的事了
than over-familiarity with someone's toilet routine.
我深表赞同
I can vouch for that.
-喂  -不是说你  说他
- Hey. - Not you, him.
哦  谢谢
Oh. Thanks.
不过  你的可真让人开眼了
Although yours was an eye-opener.
别担心  佩妮
Don't worry, Penny.
你是我带的伴儿  你跟我住
You're my plus-one. You'll bunk with me.
另外  旅行会让我便秘
And FYI, travel makes me constipated
所以  我是理想的酒店住宿室友
so I'm the ideal hotel roommate.
好极了
Terriffic.
还没到吗
Are we there yet?
我希望我们能赶得上主题致辞
I hope we get there in time to see the keynote address.
真的吗  你想看主题致辞
Really? You want to see the keynote?
对  听起来很有意思
Yeah, it sounds fun.
"超级细菌
"Super bacteria:
末日启示  还是令人激动的研究机会"
global apocalypse or exciting research opportunity?"
事实上  我想得是  我们直接去房间
Actually, I was thinking we could go straight to the room
然后  "休整"一下
and... take a nap.
真的吗
Really?
不去看主题致辞了
And miss the keynote?
回头能在C-SPAN上看到的
We can watch it later on C-SPAN.
而且  我真的很期待  你和我
Besides, I was really looking forward to you and me...
一起在酒店里"休整"
napping together in the hotel.
亲爱的  你那么困的话
Honey, if you're that tired
就在车里先睡上一觉吧
why don't you just take a nap here in the car?
不  你看  不是
No, see, it's not...
等一下  莱纳德来电话
Hang on. It's Leonard.
嗨  莱纳德
Hi, Leonard.
嗨  我刚收到拉杰的短信
Yeah, hi. Listen, I just got a text from Raj.
他让我告诉你
He wanted me to tell you
霍华德说的"休整"  是"做爱"的意思
that when Howard says "Nap  " He means "Sex."
谢谢你  拉杰
Thank you, Raj.
你是錒系元素的一种吗
Are you... an element in the actinoid series?
不是
No.
艾米
Amy?
你在自然界中是放射性的吗
Are you usually radioactive when found in nature?
不是
No.
你是镧系元素吗
Are you in the lanthanoid series?
艾米  轮到佩妮了
Amy, it's Penny's turn.
佩妮
Penny?
呃  我咋知道
Uh, I don't know...
你是吃的吗
Are you food?
这就是你不对了
That's not apropos.
不是说明白了吗  在元素周期表里[直译:桌]
We've already established I'm found in the periodic table.
好歹是张桌  不是吗
Well, it's a table, right?
是桌子干嘛不能放吃的
I mean, why can't there be food on it?
就知道她不配坐领头车
I knew she wasn't lead car materiel.
谁选你当了汽车旅行之王了
Who elected you Road Trip God?
莱纳德
Leonard.
那是深夜投票
It was a late-night vote.
大家都精疲力尽了
We were all exhausted
他威胁我们不选他就不让睡
and he was threatening to filibuster.
也不是啥"汽车旅行之王"啦
It's not technically "Road Trip God""
是旅途监督员
it's Travel Supervisor.
尽管汽车旅行之王听着更拉风一些
Although Road Trip God does have a certain ring to it.
我就不明白了  你们怎么就
I don't understand why you people
让他这么欺负你们啊
just let him bully you like this.
该有人奋起反抗
Someone should stand up to him.
他能怎么着
What's he going to do?
真不敢相信  你们就眼看着他把我轰出来
I can't believe you let him kick me out of the car.
我们敢怎样啊  他是旅程监督人
What could we do? He's the Travel Supervisor.
别担心  佩妮  反正这辆车更赞
Don't worry, Penny. This is a better car anyway.
没错  这是爱爱车喔
Yeah. It's the Love Car.
还用问么
Should I ask?
*他们说我们太小还不懂得*
*They say we're young and we don't know*
*长大后才能领悟*
*We won't find out until we grow*
*我不知这正确与否*
*Well, I don't know if all that's true*
*因为宝贝  我们拥有彼此*
*'Cause you got me, and, baby, I got you*
*宝贝*
*Babe*
*我拥有你*
*I got you, babe*
红一号  我真的错了
Red Leader, I'm really sorry.
*我拥有你  宝贝*
*I got you, babe.*
*I got you, babe...*
我想你了
I missed you.
知道不  我也无比想你
You know what? I missed you, too.
伯纳黛特
Bernadette?
天呐  格伦
Oh, my God, Glenn!
见到你真高兴
Great to see you!
你是来参加研讨会的吗
Are you here for the conference?
是啊  我在全球暖化座谈组
Yeah, I'm doing a global warming panel.
真不错
Oh, good for you.
格伦  这是霍华德  我男朋友
Uh, Glenn, this is my boyfriend Howard.
-很高兴认识你  -嗨
- Nice to meet you. - Hi.
哎哟  嗨
Ow. Hi.
你很幸运嘛
You're a lucky man.
妮妮是个好姑娘
Bernie's a great gal.
是啊  "妮妮"确实很好
Yes. "Bernie" Sure is.
我先走一步  座谈会定在明早
Well, I got to run. The panel's tomorrow morning.
主题是"忆雪: 回首往昔"
It's called, "Remembering Snow: A Look Back."
我会尽量去的
I'll try to catch it.
太好了
Oh, great.
-拜拜  -拜
- Bye. - Bye.
那个...妮妮
Hey... Bernie?
咋了
Yeah?
拜托告诉我那是你同性恋的表亲
Please tell me he's your gay cousin.
不是啊  他是我大学教授
No. He was one of my professors in college.
这样啊  算是松了口气
Oh! That's a relief.
然后我们交往过一年
Then we went out for a year.
来吧  赶紧办理入住  就能去"休整"一下啦
Come on, let's check in, so we can take that nap.
不  不一定是成比例的...
No, it's not necessarily proportional...
闭嘴
Shut up!
那个绿包是库珀博士的
That green bag is Dr. Cooper's.
多给你五美刀  拜托让他多等会
Here's an extra five. Make him wait.
直接进入"休整"了呀  好吧
Right to the nap, huh? Okay?
那个  格伦那哥们
Uh, so, this Glenn guy.
你说你们交往了一年呐
You say you went out with him for, like, a year.
咱有必要这时候讨论我的前男友吗
Do we really need to talk about my old boyfriend now?
不  大概没必要吧
No. I guess not.
他多高啊  1.93还是1.95
What is he, like, six-four, six-five?
两米啦
Six-seven.
估计不好买衣服吧
Probably has a hard time finding a suit that fits.
你有什么不爽吗
Is something bothering you?
-没  就是  -就是什么
- No. It's just... - What?
我就是想吧
I'm just thinking.
如果你和那哥们儿上过床
If you had sex with that guy
我是说  我现在也不能变得
I mean, there's nothing I can do here
更..."给力"一点
that will make any kind of... impact.
霍华德  这又不是什么比赛
Howard, it's not a contest.
我爱你  我想和你在一起
I love you. I want to be with you.
那很好啊  我也爱你  但
Yeah, great, love you, too, but...
如果是个比赛
If it were a contest
我也没机会赢啊  对吧
I wouldn't have a chance, right?
你不能这么想
You can't think that way.
对
Yep.
萎男
Loser.
霍华德  别这样
Howard, stop it.
对不起  我就是没想到
Sorry. I just never figured that
我这种人跟你这种女孩交往
a guy like me going out with a girl like you
还要跟他那种男人竞争
would ever have to compete with a guy like that.
等等  什么叫"我这种女孩"
Wait a minute, "A girl like me"? What's that mean?
我...我那个
I'm... I...
你是说我没那么辣
Are you saying you don't think I'm hot enough
配不上格伦吗
to go out with a guy like Glenn?
不  不是啊  完全跟你那意思相反
No! No, I'm saying exactly the opposite.
我太辣了  格伦配不上我吗
I'm too hot to go out with a guy like Glenn?
对啊  那就这意思吧
Yeah, let's go with that.
还是没货
Still nothing.
一小时后提醒我再试一次
Remind me to try again in an hour.
包在我身上
Will do.
那么
So...
闺蜜谈心
girl talk?
好啊
Um, sure.
你想聊啥
What do you got in mind?
你同意弗洛依德的"阴茎嫉妒"理论吗
Do you subscribe to the Freudian theory of penis envy?
呃  我还真没想过
Um, I never really thought about it.
怎么了
Why?
有时候我觉得长一根挺不错的
Sometimes I think it might be nice to have one.
真的吗
Really?
不为嘿咻  为了方便
Not for sex, for convenience.
你不能否认  比较而言
You can't deny that, by comparison
我们的内部下水系统太难伺候了
our internal plumbing is extremely high maintenance.
我也没怎么想过这个
Again, I've never given it much thought.
现在有时间啊
We have time now.
想想吧
Think about it.
太好了
Oh, good.
嗨
Hey.
我今晚能住这吗
Can I stay here tonight?
好啊  怎么了
Yeah. Why, what happened?
霍华德是个超级无敌大混蛋
Howard's a complete and total ass.
啊  我懂的  来吧
Oh, yeah, that. Come on in.
谢啦  我睡地板就好
Thanks. I'll sleep on the floor.
不用的
Not necessary.
我跟佩妮完全不介意睡一张床
Penny and I are perfectly comfortable sharing a bed.
不介意吗
We are?
当然了  我们是闺蜜嘛
Of course, we're best friends.
哦对了  博客写了
Oh, right, right, the blog.
不过  温馨提示
Word of warning, though.
我有夜惊倾向
I'm prone to night terrors
所以如果我睁眼乱踢或尖叫  别慌
so when I wake up kicking and screaming, don't panic.
把我按倒抚摸我的头发  就会没事的
Just pin me down and stroke my hair, and I'll be fine.
-嗨  我今晚能住这吗  -嘘嘘嘘
- Hey, can I stay here tonight? - Shh-shh-shh.
谢尔顿睡着了
Sheldon's asleep.
啥情况
What's going on?
这个  霍华德是个超级无敌大混蛋
Well, Howard's a complete and total ass
所以伯纳黛特占了我的床
Bernadette's in my bed
不管我怎么摸艾米的头发  她都乱咬
and no matter how much you stroke Amy's hair, she bites.
-啥  -无所谓了
- What? - Never mind.
我能住这儿不
Can I stay here or not?
-当然能  -太好了
- Uh, sure. - All right.
你想怎么睡
So, how do you want to do this?
反正打死我也不跟他睡
Well, I'm not getting in bed with him.
没错  就像是
Yeah, it is a little like
爬进了德拉库拉的棺材
getting into Dracula's coffin.
我们得充分利用这个情况
We're just gonna have to make the best of this.
好吧  你说"充分利用"的意思是
Okay, when you say "make the best of it..."
-睡觉  -好吧
- Sleep.  - Right.
我们就把中间这里叫做
So we'll just call the middle here
"中立区"
the Neutral Zone.
中什么
The what?
《星际迷航》啊
Star Trek.
中立区嘛
You know, the Neutral Zone
就在联邦和罗慕兰帝国之间
between the Federation and the Romulan Empire.
哦  好吧
Oh, okay.
就跟当年一样
Just like old times.
当然咯
Of course
有时候联邦和罗慕兰帝国
sometimes the Federation and the Romulans
会进入中立区
would enter the Neutral Zone
进行临时休战谈判
to negotiate a temporary truce.
亲爱的  我就敞开天窗说亮话吧
Sweetie, let me put this in a way you'll understand:
休想碰我的下半身
from the waist down, my shields are up.
懂了  懂了
Got it, got it.
知道吗  只用上半身
We can do all kinds of stuff
我们也可以玩出很多花样
from the waist up, you know?
-睡觉  -晚安
- Go to sleep.  - Good night.
请亲口告诉我你俩没在交媾
Please tell me you're not having coitus.
我俩没在交媾
We are not having coitus.
你俩能保证今晚一直
Can you guarantee that it won't happen
都不交媾吗
at any time during the night?
-能  -不能
- Yes.  - No.
特纳经典电影频道即将播出
Next on Turner Classic Movies
《BJ单身日记》
Bridget Jones's Diary.
哦天呐  我已经内牛满面了
Oh, my God, I'm crying already.
拉杰  拉杰
Raj? Raj?
拉杰
Raj?
我今晚得睡在这儿
I need to sleep here tonight.
为啥
Why?
霍华德是个彻头彻尾的大混蛋
Howard is a complete and total ass
伯纳黛特霸占了佩妮的床  艾米总咬人
Bernadette is in Penny's bed, Amy bites
佩妮和莱纳德有可能会交媾
and Penny may or may not have coitus with Leonard.
好吧  进来吧
Okay. Come on in.
莱纳德  你睡着了吗
Leonard, are you asleep?
没
No.
真的很感谢你今晚收留我
I really appreciate you letting me stay here tonight.
小意思  没什么
Sure, no problem.
我知道这样有点儿尴尬
I know it's kinda weird.
米错
True dat.
"米错"
"True dat"?
自从咱俩分手以后我学会了更多流行语
I've gotten a lot more street since we broke up.
好吧
Right.
还生我气吗
Still mad at me about that?
不了不了  我很理解
No. No, I understand.
我逼得太紧  你想要些空间
I got too intense, you had to back off.
谢谢
Thank you.
这方面我现在已经好多了  知道吗
I've gotten a lot better at that, you know.
我俩分手以后我跟四个女人约会过
I've dated four different women since we broke up
我没跟她们中任何一个人说过"我爱你"
and I didn't tell any of them that I loved them
和"我想和你生儿育女"
and wanted to have their babies.
真替你高兴
Good for you.
嗯  晚安
Okay, good night.
晚安
Good night.
知道吗  也许今晚突破一下中立区
You know, maybe it wouldn't be the worst idea in the world
也不是什么坏主意
to violate the Neutral Zone for just one night.
嗨  莱纳德  谢尔顿把我赶出了
Hey, Leonard, Sheldon kicked me
房间  把你房间的钥匙给我了
out of the room, gave me your key.
佩妮在这儿呢
Penny's here.
不啊  我们不想看《BJ单身日记》
No, we don't want to watch Bridget Jones's Diary!
早上好  欢迎参加"科学与社会"研讨会
Good morning and welcome to Science and Society.
我是谢尔顿·库珀
I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper
理学学士兼理学硕士兼文学硕士
BS, MS, MA
兼哲学博士兼理学博士
PhD, and ScD.
我的神呐  是吧
OMG, right?
也许这个笑话对于在座各位有点儿太弱智了
Perhaps that joke was a little too hippie-dippy for this crowd.
好了  我们开始致开幕词
All right then, we'll begin with opening remarks.
罗斯顿考斯基小姐  你愿意抛砖引玉
Miss Rostenkowski, would you like to start us off
谈谈你对于
by discussing your assessment
科学对社会的责任的看法吗
of science's responsibility to society?
好的
Sure.
我认为  每一个自然学科
I think all branches of science
在今天都需要谨慎发展
have to move cautiously these days.
能毁灭世界的
It's not just giant nuclear weapons
并不只有大型的核武器
that can destroy the world.
作为一名微生物学家  我可以告诉你
As a microbiologist, I can tell you
即使是最微小的微生物也能让你尸骨无存
even the tiniest organisms can still tear you a new one.
有意思
Interesting.
我觉得在座各位需要了解我同事的一点
I think what you might need to know about my colleague
就是尽管她声称
is that though she claims
她最感兴趣的领域是细小的微生物
her field of interest is tiny organisms
她显然在我们可以认为是大型武器的东西上
she certainly has spent her fair share of time
花了相当多的时间
around what we can assume was pretty massive weaponry.
我认为沃罗威茨先生需要记住一点
I think Mr. Wolowitz needs to keep in mind
那就是过去的事情已经过去了
that the past is the past.
但他应该知道我是那种
But he should know that I am the kind of girl
让任何"大型导弹"趋之若鹜的女孩
who could get all the giant missiles she wants.
我们在讨论女性对阴茎的渴求吗
Are we talking about women wanting penises?
因为我想插一句嘴
Because I'd like to weigh in.
库萨帕里博士  你想说几句吗
Dr. Koothrappali, would you care to join the conversation?
当然  我有两点要讲
Certainly. I'd like to raise two points.
第一  我觉得他们确实在讨论小弟弟
Number one, I think they are talking about penises.
第二  这桔汁他妈的香槟太他妈的爽了
And number two, these mimosas are kicking my little brown ass.
我真他妈的想他妈的踹你
I'd like to kick your little brown ass.
我干啥了
What did I do?
我不知道诶
Oh, I don't know.
也许当你走进一间酒店房间
Maybe when you walk into a hotel room
看见一哥们儿跟女朋友重归于好时
and you see a guy getting back together with his girlfriend
你应该考虑做点儿别的什么
you should consider doing something other
而不是爬到旁边的床上
than crawling into the adjoining bed.
是啊  你说了不能看《BJ单身日记》的
I did. You said no Bridget Jones.
我俩没有重归于好
We weren't getting back together!
只是一夜风流而已
It was a one-time thing!
对不起
Excuse me.
我们现在不接受
We're not taking comments or questions
观众的评论和提问
from the audience just yet.
闭嘴吧  谢尔顿
Oh, shut up, Sheldon!
-嗨  闺蜜  -嗨
- Hi, bestie.  - Hi.
好吧  我们为什么不试着重回正题呢
All right, why don't we see if we can bring this back to topic.
让我来问问你吧  妮妮
Let me ask you something, Bernie.
看样子不行
I guess not.
如果你碰到了我酷似安吉丽娜·朱莉的
How would you feel if you met my ex-girlfriend
前女友  你会作何感受
and she was like Angelina Jolie?
拜托  霍华德  别做梦了
Oh, come on, Howard, be realistic.
怎么  如此英俊的我难道钓不到安吉丽娜·朱莉吗
What, I'm not hot enough for Angelina Jolie?
我想插句嘴
I'd like to weigh in here.
确实钓不到
No.
好吧  我们不如开始进入
All right, why don't we open it up
观众的问答环节吧
to Q&A from the audience?
好  我有问题
Yeah, I have a question.
有谁今晚能带我离开这鬼地方
Is there anybody who can get me the hell out of here
回洛杉矶
and back to Los Angeles tonight?
我今晚开车回洛城
I'm driving back to L.A. tonight.
佩妮  那是格伦  格伦  那是佩妮
Penny, that's Glenn. Glenn, that's Penny.
不要
No!
红1号呼叫红5号
Red Leader to Red Five.
谁想玩个小游戏
Anybody up for a little game?
我心里想的是
I spy with my little eye...
一种非铁金属
a nonferrous metal.
估计是超出接收范围了
Must be out of range.
莱纳德  我能问你个问题吗
Leonard, can I ask you a question?
问吧
Sure.
你这么生气是不是因为你的前任女友
Are you bothered by the fact that your former girlfriend
和一位可能是我这辈子见过的
left the symposium with what is probably
最帅的男人一起离开研讨会了
the most beautiful man I've ever seen in my life?
不是  你为啥这么问
No. Why do you ask?
因为我们的时速达到了120英里[约193公里]
Because we're going 120 miles per hour.
好吧  如果没人想猜的话
All right, if no one's going to guess...
其实我想的是几英里前我们经过的
I was spying the aluminum rims on the police car
那辆警车的铝制轮缘
we passed a few miles back.